Guide to the Oswald G. Villard Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Oswald G. Villard papers
1932-1998
1958-1998
SC0584
Villard, Oswald G.
100 Linear feet (121 boxes)
The papers include correspondence, articles and research papers, memoranda, reports, research files, contracts, minutes, and other materials, 1958-1998. Institutions represented in the papers include Stanford University, Stanford Research Institute, Naval Research Advisory Committee, USAF Scientific Advisory Board, Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, Union of Radio Science International, and the Voice of America. The collection also includes instruction manuals and a log for radio station W6YX, 1932-1933 (club station at Stanford)
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
This collection was given to the Stanford University Archives in 1998 by Oswald G. Villard.
Information about Access
The collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 48 hours in advance of intended use.
Biographical/Historical note
O. G. Villard, Jr., a leader in electromagnetic theory and experimental methods, earned his engineer's degree in 1943 and his Ph.D. in 1949 at Stanford, studying with Dr. F. E. Terman. He joined the faculty in Stanford's electrical engineering department and later was one of the founders of the Stanford Research Institute, now SRI International. He is a member of the National Academy of Sciences and the National Academy of Engineering and a fellow of the IEEE and the American Association for the Advancement of Science.
Scope and Content
The papers include correspondence, articles and research papers, memoranda, reports, research files, contracts, minutes, and other materials, 1958-1998. Institutions represented in the papers include Stanford University, Stanford Research Institute, Naval Research Advisory Committee, USAF Scientific Advisory Board, Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, Union of Radio Science International, and the Voice of America. The collection also includes instruction manuals and a log for radio station W6YX, 1932-1933 (club station at Stanford)
Access Terms
Naval Research Advisory Committee.; Stanford Research Institute.; Stanford University. Department of Electrical Engineering. Faculty.; Electrical engineering --Study and teaching.
Collection Contents
- ESD - DAG (Electronic Systems Division - Division Advisory Group) bulk data, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- ESD - DAG correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- ESD - DAG correspondence, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- ESD - DAG correspondence, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ESD - DAG correspondence, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- ESD - DAG meeting, 1/18/1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- ESD - DAG meeting, 3/20/1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- ESD - DAG meeting, 10/29/1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- ESD - DAG correspondence, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ESD - DAG various periodicals: Arctic, Defense Industry Bulletin, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- ESD - DAG meeting, 7/20/1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ESD - DAG correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- ESD - DAG correspondence, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- ESD - DAG meeting, 9/19/1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- ESD - DAG correspondence, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- ESD - DAG correspondence, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- ESD - DAG meeting, 2/13/1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- ESD - DAG meeting, 5/9/1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- ESD - DAG meeting, 9/6/1974 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- ESD - DAG correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- NRAC - LAB (Naval Research Advisory Committee - Laboratory Advisory Board) air warfare, 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- NRAC - LAB undersea warfare, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- NRAC - LAB personnel, 1971-1974 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- NRAC - LAB ordnance, 1970-1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- NRAC bulk data, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- NRAC bulk data, 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- NRAC Subcommittee on U.S. Naval Ordnance Lab, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- NRAC & subcommittee member roster, 1969-1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- NRAC meetings, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- NRAC correspondence, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- NRAC meetings, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- NRAC correspondence, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- NRAC meeting, 4/1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- NRAC meetings, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- NRAC meeting, 7/1973 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- NRAC Computer Utilization Committee meeting, 10/3/1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- NRAC Laboratory Computer Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- NRAC correspondence, 1-6/1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- NRAC Life Sciences Coordinating Committee, 1968-1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- NRAC Marine Corps Panel, 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- NSA - SAB (National Security Agency - Scientific Advisory Board) meeting, 6/15-16/1978 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 9/28-29/1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 1/1979 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- NSA – SAB meeting, 6/28-29/1979 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- NSA – SAB meeting & roster, 9-10/1979 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- NSA – SAB meeting, 12/6-7/1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- NSA – SAB meeting, 3/20-21/1980 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- NSA – SAB meeting, 4/25/1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- NSA – SAB meeting, 8/11/1980 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- NSA – SAB meeting, 12/4-5/1980 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 5/27-28/1981 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 7/31/1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 9/23-24/1981 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 11/12-13/1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 12/9-10/1981 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 9/15-22/1982 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 12/1-2/1982 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 3/1-2/1983 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 6/27/1983 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 9/7-8/1983 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 12/5-12/1983 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 4/25/1984 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 5/2-3/1984 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- NSA - SAB meeting, 6/7-8/1984 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- NSA - SAB roster, 1980-1983 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- NSA - SAB DOD vouchers, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- NCS (National Cryptological School) Board of Visitors, 5/1984 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- NCS meetings, 12/1984-1/1985 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- U.S. Information Agency, 1962-1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- U.S. Navy Electronics Laboratory, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- U.S. Radio Astronomy Observatories, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- U general, 1966-1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Vehicle Security, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- W general, 1965-1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Waterman, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Washington State University, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Wave Avoidance Radar (WAR), 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Weinshel, B. O., 1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- WASC (Western Association of Schools & Colleges), 1969-1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Wilcox, John, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Whispering Gallery D-Region, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Wooden, Bruce (SPC), 1980 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- World Data Center, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- XYZ general, 1968-1973 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- DARPA (Defense Advanced Research Projects Agency) meeting on ASW program, 2/22/1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- N00014-70-C-0413 Project files, 1-4/1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Villard Questionnaires, 1/21/1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- ONR-64 (Office of Naval Research) general, 10-12/1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- REST program, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- REST bibliography, 1980-1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Villard artwork CSI, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Villard artwork CSI, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Villard artwork CSI, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- ARPANET messages, 1981-1983 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- PDC 882-072 unclassified material, 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Stanford University - Committee on Assistantships & Financial Awards, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  may contain confidential information
- Stanford University - Committee on Awards, Prizes & Honors, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Stanford University - Outside Possibilities (scholarships), 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Stanford University - Baxter Committee on Research Policy, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Stanford University - Committee on Committees of the Senate, Committee on University Libraries, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Stanford University - Editorial Committee, 1962-1965 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Stanford University - Committee on Financial Aid, 1965-1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Stanford University - Committee on Financial Awards, External, 1966-1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Stanford University - School of Engineering Advisory Council, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Stanford University - Hybrid Computer Laboratory Policy Committee, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Stanford University - Committee on Road Fund Allocation, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Stanford University - Committee on Research Policy, 1966-1970 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Stanford University - Post-Masters Committee, 1963-1966 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Stanford University - PACE Committee, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Stanford University - New Faculty Committee, 1962-193 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Stanford University - NASA Building Committee, 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Stanford University - Miscellaneous committees, 1963-1969 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Stanford University - Electrical Engineering Executive Committee, 1963-1972 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- USAF - SAB (U.S. Air Force – Scientific Advisory Board) Task Force on Lightning Warning Devices, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- USAF – SAB Terrain Evaluation Study Group, 1965-1967 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- USAF – SAB Geophysics Panel (Solar) (Box 9, Folder 4)
- USAF – SAB Geophysics Panel (Meteorology), 1964-1967 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- NSA – SAB Signal Acquisition & Initial Processing Subcommittee, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- NSA – SAB, 1977-1984 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- NSA – SAB Public Cryptography, 1971-1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- NSA – SAB Public Cryptography, 1978-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- NSA – SAB Public Cryptography meeting 9/22/1978 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- NSA – SAB Public Cryptography clippings, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- NSA – SAB Public Cryptography 5/11-12/1978 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- NSA – SAB Public Cryptography meeting 7/19-20/1978 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- DSB (Defense Science Board), 1966-1970 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- DSB, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- DSB reports, periodicals, 1972-1974 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- DSB member roster, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- DSB Panel meeting, 1/16-17/1980 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- DSB Panel meeting, 3/24-25/1980 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- DSB Panel meeting, 4/17-18/1980 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- DSB Panel meeting, 5/23/1980 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- DSB Task Force, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- DSB, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- DSB meeting, 10/10-11/1974 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- DSB, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- DSB IR&D meeting, 6/24-25/1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- DSB IR&D meeting, 5/13-14/1974 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Van Every, Al: presentation, 4/2/1976 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Project files, 7-12/1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Project files, 1-6/1977 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- ESD TAG (Technical Advisory Group), ONR JJK meetings, 5/1977 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Project files, 7-12/1977 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- ELF Monitoring, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- ESD TAG meeting, 2/22/1978 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Project files, 1-6/1978 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- SRI memos report distribution, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- AFSB (Air Force Studies Board) meeting, 11/18-19/1976 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- AFSB Pulsed Power Sources Summer Study, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- AFSB meeting, 3/10-11/1977 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- AFSB Data Link Technology Panel, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- AFSB Data Link Technology meeting, 5/20/1977 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- AFSB meeting, 6/16-17/1977 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- AFSB meeting, 11/17-18/1977 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- AFSB panel meeting, 5/17/1978 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- AFSB meeting, 12/4-5/1978 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- AFSB meeting, 2/4-5/1982 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- AFSB, 1976-1982 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- AFSB, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- AFSB meeting, 6/10-11/1976 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- AFSB publications, 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Electromagnetic Fields Proposal, 1979 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Fraser-Smith, Tony, 1977-1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Fraser-Smith, Tony, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Stanford University - Committee on Undergraduate Administration, 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Stanford University - Committee on Undergraduate Administration, 1966-1968 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Stanford University - Committee on University Libraries, 1968-1972 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Stanford University - Electronics Laboratories Report Publication List, 1972-1974 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Stanford University – Centrex Billing Statements, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Stanford University - ONR Contract N00014-83-K (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Stanford University - B.C. – 10474 Investigation of Ionospheric Processes (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Villard consultant contracts, 1964-1968 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Villard personal correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Villard consultant contracts, 1969-1981 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Villard correspondence, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Villard correspondence, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Villard correspondence, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Villard correspondence, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Villard correspondence, 1-6/1982 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Villard correspondence, 7-12/1982 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Villard correspondence, 1-6/1983 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Villard correspondence, 7-12/1983 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Abstracts, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Sybil Terman Fund, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- CAC / ACFS, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Villard chronological file, 1-5/1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Villard chronological file, 6-8/1984 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Villard chronological file, 9-12/1984 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Villard PSRs, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Villard PSRs, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Villard chronological file, 9-12/1988 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous publications, 1979-1997 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- NAS (National Academy of Sciences) Ad Hoc Committee, Sanguine project, 1971 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Villard correspondence, 1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Villard correspondence, 7-12/1976 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Villard correspondence, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Mills College Advisory Council, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- ONR Symposium, 10/27-28/1976 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Villard MVY Experiments, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous publications (reports, reprints), 1978-1980 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous publications, 1968-1974 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Miscellaneous publications, 1975-1979 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Moxon, Les, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- LDE (Long Delay Echo Effect) data sheets, Banks – Meacham (Box 22, Folder 163)
- LDE data sheets, Means – Williams (Box 23, Folder 132)
- QST magazine (amateur radio), 1979-1983 (Box 23, Folder 33)
- NAS reports, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Villard personal correspondence, 1-6/1975 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Villard personal correspondence, 1-6/1976 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Villard correspondence, 7-12/1976 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Villard correspondence, 1-6/1977 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Villard correspondence, 7-12/1977 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Villard correspondence, 1-6/1978 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Villard correspondence, 7-12/1978 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Villard correspondence, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Villard correspondence, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Villard correspondence, 1-6/1981 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Villard correspondence, 7-12/1981 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Villard correspondence, 10-12/1965 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Villard correspondence, 1-3/1966 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Villard correspondence, 4-6/1966 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Villard correspondence, 7-9/1966 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Villard correspondence, 10-12/1966 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Villard correspondence, 1/1967 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Villard correspondence, 1/1968 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Villard correspondence, 1-6/1969 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Villard correspondence, 7-9/1969 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Villard correspondence, 10-12/1969 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Villard correspondence, 1-6/1970 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Villard correspondence, 7-12/1970 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Villard correspondence, 1-6/1971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Villard correspondence, 7-12/1971 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Villard correspondence, 1-6/1972 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Villard correspondence, 7-12/1972 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Villard correspondence, 1-3/1973 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Villard correspondence, 4-12/1973 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Villard chronological file, 1-4/1985 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Villard chronological file, 4-8/1985 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Villard chronological file, 9-12/1985 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Villard chronological file, 1-4/1986 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Villard chronological file, 5-8/1986 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Villard chronological file, 9-12/1986 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Villard chronological file, 1-4/1987 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Villard chronological file, 5-8/1987 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Villard chronological file, 9-12/1987 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Villard chronological file, 1-4/1988 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Villard chronological file, 5-8/1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Villard chronological file, 1-4/1989 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Villard chronological file, 5-8/1989 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Villard chronological file, 9-12/1989 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Villard chronological file, 1-4/1990 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- 2495 project/SONAR, 1981 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- experiments & memoranda, 1968-1971 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Los Banos experiments, 1968-1970 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- NRAC instruction notebook (Box 33, Folder 4)
- NRAC member roster, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- NRAC biographies, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
- SRI memos, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- SRI Memos, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
- 2495 project status reports (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Flanagan, Roger J., 1965 (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Gilliland, Clint, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Harker, K. J., 1971-1980 (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Jensen, Jerry G., 1969 (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Katsufrakis, John Peter, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Kastilahn, Bill, 1970 (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Kawachika, Norman, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 8)
- Lynch, Jack, 1970-197 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Murphy, Ron, 1964-1965 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Cole, Charlie, 1982-1984 (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Fraser-Smith, A. C., 1982-1984 (Box 35, Folder 12)
- Fraser-Smith, A. C., 1984 (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Fraser-Smith, A. C., 1983 (Box 35, Folder 14)
- Fraser-Smith, A. C., 1982 (Box 35, Folder 15)
- Fraser-Smith, A. C., 1981 (Box 35, Folder 16)
- Fraser-Smith, A. C. resume, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Fraser-Smith, A. C., 1980 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Knausenberger, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- General Radio Company, 1960-1968 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Goodacre, Alan – LDE paper, 1980-1983 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Goree, William S., 1978 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Goumas, George G., 1983 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Graf, Calvin, 1958-1979 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Granger Associates, 1964-1968 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- H general, 1963-1971 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- HALE V program, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Hill panel, 1963-1964 (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Hoptoad project, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Hynek, Prof. J. Allen, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 14)
- Hazen, David C., 1980 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- I general, 1968-1970 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- IFR project, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- IBM Honors Co-Op – Advisees, 1968-69 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Institute for Defense Analysis, 1964-1968 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- JINDALEE Communications, 1974-1981 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Journal of Geophysical Research, 1964-65 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Journal of Geophysical Research, 1963 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- JSEP Supported Research Projects, 1968-1969 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Jason Summer Study, 1981-1983 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- K general, 1964-1976 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Kahn correspondence and patent, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Kinoy, Prof. Ward Beecher (memorial resolution), 1965 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Bracewell, Ronald, 1965-1972 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Bubenik, David, 1968-1977 (Box 37, Folder 13)
- Cold Antennas articles, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Buxton, Jim, 1974-1977 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Croft, Thomas A., 1965-1970 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- High Frequency Antennas for Skywave Reception, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Pierce, Edward T., 1974-1976 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Platteville Heating Schedule, 1971 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Power Lines, 1962-1966 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- President's Committee on the National Medal of Science, 1968-1972 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- PSAC (President's Science Advisory Committee) meeting, 2/24-25/1969 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- PSAC, 1962-1972 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Program, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- TAG meeting, 1/20/1981 (Box 38, Folder 12)
- Project files, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Project files, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 14)
- Project files, 7-12/1980 (Box 38, Folder 15)
- Project files, 1-6/1980 (Box 38, Folder 16)
- TN -10, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 17)
- TN -8, 1977-1978 (Box 38, Folder 18)
- Ocean Surveillance, 1978-1979 (Box 38, Folder 19)
- Office, lab & site matters, 1965 (Box 38, Folder 20)
- ONR selection panel, 1971-192 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- P general, 1967-1974 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Patent – feedback loop selector, 1965 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Personnel – general, 1965-1972 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Project files, 1-6/1974 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Project files, 7-12/1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Project files, 1-6/1973 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- SCOE meeting, 6/17-18/1974 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Q general, 1967-1978 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Villard QST article on Ivory Coral, 1974 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- R General, 1965-1983 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- RADAM 658D32 CNP, 1974-1977 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Stanford University - Academic Council, 1964-1967 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Stanford University - Academic Council, 1968-1970 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Stanford University - Academic Council, 1971-1972 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- A general, 1963-1984 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Aerophone, 1975 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Anastassiades, Prof. Michael, 1963-1967 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Apollo XVII Surface Electrical Properties Experiment report, MIT, 1972 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Arecibo meeting, 11/7-8/1967 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- ARPANET, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- ARRL talk, 1980 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Army Security Agency, 1965-1967 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- ASEE Westinghouse Award, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Clements, Tom, 1969 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Corcoran, John J., 1969-1970 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Croft, Dr. Thomas A., 1965-1966 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Croft, Dr. Thomas A., 1967-1973 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Da Rosa, Dr. Aldo, 1967-1972 (Box 41, Folder 12)
- D general, 1968-1973 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Defense Communication Agency, 1965 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Dislocation, 1973 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Dingle, Bruce, 1970-1971 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Dougherty, Steven, 1967-1971 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Stanford University - Electrical Engineering Department faculty, 1963-1966 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Stanford University - Electrical Engineering Department faculty, 1967-1970 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Stanford University - Electrical Engineering Department faculty, 1971 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Stanford University - Electrical Engineering Department faculty, 1972-1987 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Stanford University - Electrical Engineering Department, proposed antenna course (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Epstein, Mark R., 1964-1975 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- E general, 1968-1972 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Earthquakes, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- ELF monitoring, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- End Fire Pair, 1973 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Engineering Science Management Council, 1977-1978 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Environmental Science Services Administration (Dept. of Commerce), 1966-1971 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Exempt project, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- F general, 1967-1976 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Federal Scientific Corporation, 1965-1966 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Fenwick, Dr. Robert B., 1964-1968 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Ferrell, Perry (Gilfer Associates, Inc.), 1983 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Foghorns, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 12)
- Fox, Paul, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 13)
- Freeway problem, 1963-1969 (Box 43, Folder 14)